itsup.com 2018-12-31

# ItsUp.com Privacy Policy / itsup.com

## ITS UP PRIVACY POLICY

### Introduction

Thank you for visiting www.itsup.com (“Site”), and, if applicable, choosing to use our products and services including (collectively the “Service”). The Site is owned by SCTR Services, LLC (“Its Up”). We try to make our Privacy Policy easy to understand so that you are informed as to how we use your information. This Privacy Policy, is an integral part of using our Service and Site; therefore you must completely agree to our Privacy Policy and be over the age of 18 to use our Site or Service. 

### Information Collected

##### Personally Identifiable Information Collected Via the Site

You will not be required to provide us any information when you visit our Site. Portions of our Site may require you to submit personally identifiable information to us. During your use of the Site we may collect your name, email, address, telephone number, date of birth, and other identifying details. Any personally identifiable information you submit via the Site shall be used and disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition to the personally identifiable information collected we may also collect your payment information including but not limited to credit card information, tax ID, banking information, or other information to process or issue payments.

##### Non-Identifying Information

Whenever you use our Site or Service, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as information regarding your browsing habits and your use of the Site, IP address, interactions with the Site and Service, query information, location information, pricing data, research history, location and GPS information, referring URL, browser, application interaction, mobile provider information, operating system, data usage, data transferred, and Internet Service Provider. 

### Use of Your Information

This section explains how we plan on using your information collected by us. In order to use our Service or Site, you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information:

  * To enhance or improve your user experience.
  * To improve the Site and Service.
  * To email you newsletters and marketing as required.
  * To understand how you communicate and use our Service or Site.
  * To contact and correspond with you and to respond to your inquiries.

Additionally, we may give your information to law enforcement if we are compelled to by a court order, if there has been a violation of any American laws, EU laws or if a violation of any other agreements or the Privacy Policy has occurred.

### Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information

If you have submitted information to our Site you will be unable to edit that information. However, when using our Service you may be able to access and edit your information via the Site dashboard. You will be unable to opt out of any of our data collection practices. If at any time, you have any questions or wish to review, change, or delete any of your information collected by us, please contact us at contact@itsup.com. Additionally, if you would like us to permanately remove any accessible copies of your information, please contact us at contact@itsup.com. After you have cancelled your account please be aware that we may keep inaccessible copies of your information for a commercially reasonable period of time.

### Cookies and Other Tracking

Cookies are small bits of code that help us identify you as an individual. Our current Site uses cookies to track your advertisements. You may disable cookies via your browser settings; however, disabiling cookies may result in undesired performance when accessing the Site. Additionaly, the Site employs pixel tracking to understand what portions of the Site you have visited.

### Third Party Access to Your Information

Although you are entering into an Agreement with Its Up to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others to allow you to access the Site and Service.

Throughout the course of our provision of our services to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our Service or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you. 

### Law Enforcement

You agree that we may disclose your information to authorities if compelled to by a court order. Additionally, you agree that we may disclose your information if we reasonably believe that you have violated American laws or the terms of our Privacy Policy or if we believe that a third party is at risk of bodily harm. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is proper to do so for legal reasons, where your actions violate any law of the United States of America or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our Site or this agreement. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities and to any government authorities, as required.

### Commercial, Non-Commercial Communications and Do Not Track

If you decide to provide us with your contact information, you agree that we may send you communications via text and email. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying Its Up that you no longer wish to receive these communications, we will endeavour to promptly remove you from our notification listgins once we have received that request. We currently do not offer website functionality for you to opt out through “do not track” listings. If you wish to opt out of certain communications or information collection, please contact us at contact@itsup.com. 

### Third Parties

Its Up may post links to third party websites on our Site, which may include information that we have no control over. When accessing a third party site through our Site or Service, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties. Its Up bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. You must review their Terms of Service and Privacy to understand how their information collection practices work.

### Security Measures

We make reasonable attempts to protect your information by using physical and electronic safeguards. For these reasons Its Up uses SSL certificates. However, as our Service and Site are hosted electronically we can make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information. For this reason, we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats.   

### Your California Privacy Rights

Its Up permits residents of the State of California to use its Service, and complies with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. Although we do not disseminate your information to third parties without permission, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at contact@itsup.com with any questions.

### Age Compliance

We intend to fully comply with American and international laws respecting children’s privacy. Therefore, we do not collect or process any information for any persons under the age of 18. If you are under 18 please do not access the Service or Site.

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. We may transfer personal information to the United States or elsewhere and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Merger and Acquisition

In the event that the Its Up is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. Please be aware that once the information is transferred your privacy rights may change.

### Amendments

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will modify the date listed on this Agreement or we may contact you. You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site and Service. If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site and Service and notify us of your refusal to agree by e-mailing us at contact@itsup.com.

Last Modified: November 11, 2015
